Mona Shaban Frontend Developer

mona00mona1997@gmail.com

+972599923814

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/monamohammed1997/

Rafah, Palestine

★ Portfolio

ttps://www.facebook.com/monamohammedshaban97/

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer with an excellent experience in the field.

I am always passionate about learning and undertaking new challenges, constantly evolving, and enjoying dealing with problems and solving them.

I look forward to an opportunity where I can exploit my skills and further develop them, I have the capability and confidence to work independently or within a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

02/2023 - 09/2023

Frontend Developer (React.js), Al-Qeeq Company

Gaza, Palestine

• Responsible for developing interfaces for websites and dashboards.

03/2023 - 03/2023

Frontend Developer

Saudi Arabia

Dashboard

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

02/2023 - 02/2023

Frontend Developer

Gaza, Palestine

Lawyers Dashboard

- Convert PSD using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

02/2023 - 02/2023

Frontend Developer

Turkey

Dashboard

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

10/2022 - 12/2022

React.js Developer, Ajyal Incubator

Gaza

Landing Page and Dashboard

- Responsible for building the UI using components.
- Using styled-components, bootstrap, reactstrap, ckeditor5-react.
- API integration using redux-thunk, and redux-saga.
- Applying responsive web design techniques.
- Working within a team.

09/2022 - present

Frontend Developer, *FoxyTech Company* □

Istanbul, Turkey

part-time

• Responsible for developing interfaces for websites.

06/2022 - 09/2022

Frontend Trainer, Safi Design

Khanyounes, Palestine

- Frontend Development (70 hrs) HTML/ HTML5
- CSS/ CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- GitHub

2022 **Emirates**

Frontend Developer, freelance-arabia

Project modification

An Arab platform for freelance work.

- I worked on the project with a team on Github.
- Developed some pages and developed a chat page.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

2022

Frontend Developer, Mohtawa company

Kuwait

Website

An introductory website for a Saudi company working in the field of e-marketing and managing social media platforms.

- Developed the interfaces using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design for all screens.
- Add animation to a website.

2021 - 2021

Frontend Developer, Highnox

Sweden

Dashboard for the accountants' program.

- Convert UI/UX design to a perfect pixel dashboard.
- Using HTML, pure CSS.
- Use charts and the Drag and Drop technique.

2021

Frontend Developer, Krogarna.se

Sweden

A dashboard is special for selling courses so that free courses or for a fee are uploaded, and a certificate is given at the end of the course.

The interfaces of three sections of this dashboard have been developed, one for admin, one for employees, and one for students.

- Convert UI/UX using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design.

2021

Frontend Developer, Al-sharq Feloowship Program

Palestine

Educational Website

- Convert Figma design using Bootstrap.
- Responsible for a responsive design for all screens.

2021

React.js Developer, GGateway

Palestine **ProShop Store**

- Responsible for building the UI.
- API integration using React-redux.
- Using redux-thunk as a middleware.
- Responsible for the high performance of the website.
- Applying responsive web design techniques.

EDUCATION

08/2015 - 12/2020

BA, Al Quds Open University

Rafah, Palestine

Computer Information System

SKILLS

• React.js

- React-redux
- Redux-toolkit
- HTML/5

CSS/3

- JavaScript
- jQuery

• Bootstrap

GitHub

Sass

- Responsive design
- API integration

- Styled-component
- Redux-thunk
- React-router
- · React-hooks

• React-Bootstrap



Arabic

English